Guide to the Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated RL.11128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2006, 4
  - Social Service/Educational, 2006; 33
    - History Channel/American Association for State and Local History (AASLH): Save Our History, 2006 (Box 28)
    - History Channel/NYC Marketing: Heritage Tourism Partnership, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Honeywell International: Honeywell NASA's FMA Live!, 2006; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Honeywell/ National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: Got 2B Safe!, 2006 (Box 28)
    - HSBC: Your Money Counts Financial Education Program, 2006; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - HSBC: Your Money Counts Financial Education Program, 2006 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 29)
    - Multiple/Home Safety Council: Home Safety Ranger Training for Kids and Families, 2006 (Box 29)
    - Samsung/Microsoft: Hope for Education, 2006 (Box 29)
    - Scholastic: Writing and Scholarship Planning for College-Bound Students, 2006 (Box 29)
    - Social Security Administration: A Ticket to Work--It Pays to Check It Out!, 2006 (Box 29)
    - Social Security Administration: A Ticket to Work--It Pays to Check It Out!, 2006 (Box 30)
  - Transactional, 2006; 34
    - Blockbuster/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Reward the Future, 2006 (Box 30)
    - Friendly Ice Cream/Easter Seals: Cones for Kids, 2006 (Box 30)
    - Harris Nesbitt/YAI/National Institute for People with Disabilities: Equity Through Education, 2006 (Box 30)
    - Linens'n Things/National Breast Cancer Foundation: Linens'n Things Pink Card, 2006 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 30)
- 2007, 5
  - Environmental/Animal, 2007; 35
    - Doubletree Hotels/World Wildlife Fund: Teaching Kids to Care, 2007 (Box 30)
    - Travelocity/Conservation Fund: Travelocity "Go Zero" Initiative, 2007 (Box 30)
  - Event, 2007; 36
    - Boost Mobile/RockCorps, 2007 (Box 30)
    - Boost Mobile/RockCorps, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Cartoon Network/National PTA: Rescuing Recess, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Dr. Phil Show/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Every Child Deserves a Toy, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Esquire Magazine/Capian Enterprises: Esquire Home 360, 2007 (Box 31)
    - FedEx/Christmas Spirit Foundation: Trees for Troops, 2007 (Box 31)
    - McDonald's: Don't Drink and Drive, Ride and Dine, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Sunkist Growers/Manning Selvage Lee: Take a Stand, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Target Volunteers: Happy Book Day Dr. Seuss!, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Target Volunteers: Happy Book Day Dr. Seuss!, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Target Volunteers: Happy Book Day Dr. Seuss!--felt hat, 2007 (Box OV13)
    - T-Mobile/City Year/Afterschool Alliance: Huddle Up, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Health-Related, 2007; 37
    - Allergan/Society for Women's Health Research: Vital Insights into Eye Wellness, 2007 (Box 31)
    - NBA/United Nations Foundation: Nothing but Nets, 2007 (Box 31)
    - NBA/United Nations Foundation: Nothing but Nets, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Procter & Gamble (Pantene Pro-V)/Entertainment Industry Foundation: Pantene Beautiful Lengths, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Joint Message, 2007; 38
    - Becton, Dickinson: Trusted Partners, 2007; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Esquire Magazine/Oxfam: House 360 Charity Auction, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Frito-Lay/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Destination Joy, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Green Mountain Coffee Roasters/PBS: PBS Blend (Fair Trade), 2007 (Box 32)
    - Home Depot/American Red Cross: Home Depot In-Store Preparedness Clinics, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Microsoft Online Services/United Nations High Commission on Refugees (UNHCR): ninemillion.org, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Procter & Gamble (Bounty)/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Bounty Cards that Count, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Schering-Plough/National Brain Tumor Foundation: Personal Reflections--Patient Stories of Brain Tumor, 2007 (Box 32)
    - School of Visual Arts/International Rescue Committee: What Happens in Darfur Happens to Us (Milton Glaser design), 2007 (Box 32)
    - School of Visual Arts/International Rescue Committee: What Happens in Darfur Happens to Us (Milton Glaser design), 2007 (Box OV10)
    - Target/National Cherry Blossom Festival, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Virgin Mobile/YouthNoise: The RE*Generation, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Volvo North America/Multiple nonprofit: Volvo for Life Awards, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Volvo North America/Multiple nonprofit: Volvo for Life Awards, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Volvo North America/Multiple nonprofit: Volvo for Life Awards (button), 2007 (Box OV13)
  - Multiple Categories, 2007; 39
    - Becton, Dickinson: Trusted Partners, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Bon Ton Stores/Goodwill Industries: The Goodwill Sale, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Canon/Sony/Multiple nonprofit: The Rimington Trophy, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Canon/Sony/Multiple nonprofit: The Rimington Trophy, 2007 (Box OV3)
    - Clorox (Glad)/Keep America Beautiful: Glad to Help, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Colgate-Palmolive/Reading is Fundamental: Healthy Bedtime Habits for a Lifetime, 2007; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Colgate-Palmolive/Reading is Fundamental: Healthy Bedtime Habits for a Lifetime, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Del Monte Foods (9 Lives): 9 Lives Million Cat Rescue, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Farmers Group/March of Dimes: Be a Hero for Babies Day, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Farmers Group/March of Dimes: Be a Hero for Babies Day, 2007 (Box OV1)
    - Frito-Lay (Sun Chips)/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Sun Chips Hope Shines On, 2007 (Box 33)
    - Holland America Line/Komen for the Cure: On Deck for the Cure, 2007; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - J.C. Penney Afterschool Fund, 2007 (Box 33)
    - J.C. Penney Afterschool Fund, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Pearson/Jumpstart: Jumpstart's Read for the Record, 2007; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Target/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Thanks and Giving, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Target/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Thanks and Giving (star and angel tree ornaments), 2007 (Box OV13)
  - National/Local Integration, 2007; 40
    - Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Day for Kids, 2007 (Box OV3)
    - Cartoon Network/National PTA: Rescuing Recess, 2007; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - CVS/Pharmacy: CVS All Kids Can, 2007; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Gold's Gym/American Diabetes Association: Cure, Care, Commitment Meets Life-Changing Results/Tour de Cure, 2007 (Box 34)
    - Gold's Gym/American Diabetes Association: Cure, Care, Commitment Meets Life-Changing Results/Tour de Cure, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Hampton Hotels: Save a Landmark, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Hollywood Entertainment/Starlight Starbright Children's Foundation: Community Spotlight--Starlight Starbright, 2007; 3 folders (Box 35)
    - Home Depot/Hands On Network: Corporate Month of Service, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Multiple/Center for Companies that Care: Caredays, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Target/American Red Cross: First Aid and Emergency Preparedness Guide, 2007 (Box 35)
    - Target/Minneapolis Institute of the Arts, 2007; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Target/Minneapolis Institute of the Arts, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Target/National Association of Town Watch: National Night Out, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Target/National Association of Town Watch: National Night Out (Frisbie, chalk), 2007 (Box OV13)
    - Target/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Elephant Gift Card, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Target/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Elephant Gift Card (elephant plush toys), 2007 (Box OV13)
  - Print Creative, 2007; 41
    - Business Week/National Organization on Disability, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Eton Corporation/American Red Cross: American Red Cross Emergency Radios by Eton, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Procter & Gamble/UNICEF: Trick or Treat for UNICEF, 2007 (Box 36)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2007; 42
    - Cartoon Network/National PTA: Rescuing Recess, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Charles and Helen Schwab Foundation/Time Warner Global Media Foundation: Schwab Learning, 2007 (Box 36)
    - ChoicePoint/National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: ChoicePoint's ADAM, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Colgate-Palmolive/Reading is Fundamental: Healthy Bedtime Habits for a Lifetime, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Fireman's Fund Insurance: Fireman's Fund Heritage, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Friendly Ice Cream/Easter Seals: Cones for Kids, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Game Show Network (GSN)/Detroit Public Schools: National Vocabulary Championship, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Honeywell/ National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: Got 2B Safe!, 2007; 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Honeywell Hometown Solutions/U.S. Space and Rocket Center: Honeywell Educators at Space Academy, 2007 (Box 36)
    - Mars (Pedigree): Pedigree Adoption Drive, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Mars (Pedigree): Pedigree Adoption Drive, 2007 (Box OV5)
    - Samsung: Four Seasons of Hope, 2007 (Box 37)
  - Transactional, 2007; 43
    - Hard Rock Café/Leary Firefighters Foundation: Firefighters Eat Free at Hard Rock Cafés Worldwide, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Macy's/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Macy's Thanks for Sharing, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Target/American Red Cross: First Aid and Emergency Preparedness Guide, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Target/Salvation Army: Salvation Army Wish List, 2007 (Box 37)
    - XanGo LLC/Operation Kids: XanGo Goodness, 2007 (Box 37)
- 2008, 6
  - Environmental/Animal, 2008; 44
    - Animal Planet/National Wildlife Federation: Backyard Habitat TV series, 2008 (Box 37)
    - JetBlue/Carbon Fund: Jetting to Green, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Live Earth: Concerts for a Planet in Crisis, 2008 (Box 37)
  - Event, 2008; 45
    - American Red Cross/Curel, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Cartoon Network/National PTA: Rescuing Recess, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Dairy Queen/Children's Miracle Network: Miracle Treat Day, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Ferrero Rocher/Share Our Strength: The Sweet Event, 2008 (Box 37)
    - Hormel Foods/America's Second Harvest: Hunger Summit, 2008; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Keen Footwear/Forty Forty: Stand Contest, 2008 (Box 38)
    - KitchenAid/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Cook for the Cure, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Multiple Schlerosis Society: Dinner of Champions/Brain Games, 2008 (Box 38)
    - OfficeMax/Adopt-a-Classroom/Maccabee Group: A Day Made Better, 2008; 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Tostitos/Habitat for Humanity, Valley of the Sun: Tostitos Team Build, 2008 (Box 38)
  - General, 2008; 46
    - Judging memo, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Supporting disks, 2008 (Box 38)
  - Health-Related, 2008; 47
    - Campbell Soup/American Heart Association: Go Red for Women, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Condé Nast Publications/Komen for the Cure: Rally for the Cure, 2008 (Box 38)
    - EMD Serono/Pfizer (Rebif)/National Multiple Schlerosis Society: Real Talk, Real Answers, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Hershey Foods/Cause/First 5 LA children's programs, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Highmark Foundation: Healthy High 5, 2008 (Box 38)
    - Liberty Mutual/American Diabetes Association: I Decide to Fight Diabetes, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Procter & Gamble (Olay)/American Society for Dermatological Surgery: Skin Cancer Takes Friends, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Supervalu (Albertson's)/Various schools: Albertson's Healthy Eaters, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Tailored Marketing-Lung Cancer Alliance, 2008 (Box 39)
  - Joint Message, 2008; 48
    - Ace Hardware/Children's Miracle Network: Racing for a Miracle, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Coors Brewing/Search Institute: MVParents.com, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Esurance/EarthCorps: Carbon Offset Day, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Esurance/EarthCorps: Carbon Offset Day, 2008 (Box OV8)
    - Esurance/Live Earth: Save Our Selves, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Operation Kids: Expect More Signing Day t-shirt, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Target/Salvation Army/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Twice Nice--Gifts for a Cause, 2008; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Target/Salvation Army/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Twice Nice--Gifts for a Cause, 2008 (Box OV8)
  - Multiple Categories, 2008; 49
    - AT, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Coors Brewing/Search Institute: MVParents.com, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Cotton Incorporated: Cotton from Blue to Green, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Crate & Barrel/Donors Choose: Donors Choose Gift Certificates, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Honeywell/ National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: Got 2B Safe!, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Intercontinental Hotel Group: Chase the Extraordinary, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Intercontinental Hotel Group: Chase the Extraordinary, 2008 (Box OV5)
    - Intercontinental Hotels (Holiday Inn Express)/Reading is Fundamental: Stay Smart Program, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Mars (Pedigree): Pedigree Adoption Drive, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Operation Kids/Drew Brees Foundation: Dream Found, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Operation Kids/Drew Brees Foundation: Dream Found, 2008 (Box OV5)
    - Produce for Kids/PBS: Produce for Kids/PBS Kids, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Supervalu (Albertson's)/Various schools: Albertson's Healthy Eaters, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Target/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Gifts for Greater Good, 2008 (Box OV5)
    - T.J. Maxx/Save the Children: Back to School Happy Hearts, 2008 (Box 40)
    - United Nations Foundation: Nothing but Nets (malaria), 2008; 3 folders (Box 40)
  - National/Local Integration, 2008; 50
    - Burlington Coat Factory/One Warm Coat: Warm Coats Warm Hearts, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Burlington Coat Factory/One Warm Coat: Warm Coats Warm Hearts poster, 2008 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Conde Nast Publications/Komen for the Cure: Rally for the Cure, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Energizer/Komen for the Cure: ReTreat Mobile Spa, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Esurance/Friends of the Urban Forest: Who Wants to Be a Superhero?, 2008 (Box 41)
    - FedEx/Christmas Spirit Foundation: Trees for Troops, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Ford/Komen for the Cure: Warriors in Pink, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Hasbro/Playskool/National Center for Boundless Playgrounds: Let's All Play...It Matters!, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Intercontinental Hotel Group: Chase the Extraordinary, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Macy's/Reading is Fundamental: Book a Brighter Future, 2008; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Macy's/Reading is Fundamental: Book a Brighter Future, 2008 (Box OV1)
    - Palm Restaurants/Dress for Success, 2008 (Box 41)
    - REI/VolunteerMatch: Get Outside, Get Involved, Get Dirty!, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Subway/American Heart Association: Start! and Fresh Fit, 2008 (Box 41)
    - T-Mobile/City Year/Afterschool Alliance: Huddle Up, 2008 (Box 41)
  - Print Creative, 2008; 51
    - Conde Nast Publications/Komen for the Cure: Rally for the Cure, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Forty Forty/Keen Footwear: Stand Contest, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Jones Apparel Group: Jones NY in the Classroom, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Macy's/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Reason to Believe, 2008 (Box 42)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2008; 52
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop: Huggable Heroes, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Cartoon Network/National PTA: Rescuing Recess, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Conde Nast Publications/Komen for the Cure: Rally for the Cure, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Cross Media Creative Group/Discovery Education: All About Computers and Cyber Security, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Esurance/California, Monte Vista High Schools: Safe Drive Stay Alive, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Game Show Network (GSN): National Vocabulary Championship, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Honeywell/U.S. Space and Rocket Center: Honeywell Educators at Space Camp, 2008 (Box 42)
    - L'Oréal/Ovarian Cancer Research Fund: Women of Worth, 2008; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Rose-Glen Group/We Love This Place!: We Love This Place! Signs, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Ruder Finn/Liz Claiborne: Love Is Not Abuse, 2008; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - State Farm: 50 Million Pound Challenge, 2008 (Box 43)
  - Transactional, 2008; 53
    - Chili's/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Create-a-Pepper, 2008; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Chili's/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Create-a-Pepper, 2008 (Box OV1)
    - Chili's/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Create-a-Pepper, 2008 (Box OV8)
    - Hard Rock International/Breast Cancer Research Foundation: Rocktober Campaign to Benefit Breast Cancer Research, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Midas/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Midas Touch Maintenance Package, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Philosophy/PBS: The Tree House Hand Care Kid, 2008 (Box 44)
    - Rock Bottom Restaurant Brewery/Various fire departments: Fire Chief Ale, 2008 (Box 44)
    - SanDisk/Alzheimer's Association: SanDisk Help Take Action Against Alzheimer's, 2008 (Box 44)
    - Scholastic Book Club/Multiple nonprofits: Classrooms Care, 2008 (Box 44)
    - Yum!/World Food Programme: World Hunger Relief Week, 2008 (Box 44)
- 2009, 7
  - Broadcast Video, 2009; 54
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2009; 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Environmental/Animal, 2009; 55
    - NASCAR/Alliance to Save Energy: Drive $marter Challenge, 2009 (Box 44)
  - Event, 2009; 56
    - A&E Network/National Council on Alcohol and Drug Dependency (NCADD): Recovery Project, 2009 (Box 44)
    - IKEA/ Georgia Campaign for Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention: It's About Time, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Jumpstart: Read for the Record, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Jumpstart: Read for the Record, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Push Creative Advertising/Alzheimer's Association: Voices Remember, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Samsung/Jor Torre Safe at Home Foundation: Four Seasons of Hope Dodger's Day, 2009 (Box 45)
    - T-Mobile/NBA/New Orleans Recovery School District: T-Mobile Huddle Up for New Orleans, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Uncle Ben's/Feeding America: Kids Café Program, 2009 (Box 45)
  - Health-Related, 2009; 57
    - CYBEX/Breast Cancer Reesearch Foundation: CYBEX Pink Ribbon Run, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Energizer/Komen for the Cure: ReTreat Mobile Spa, 2009; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Footlocker/American Cancer Society: Pink Ribbon, 2009 (Box 45)
    - NBA/United Nations Foundation: Nothing but Nets, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Preston Kelly/National Marrow Donor Program: Be the Match!, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Subway/American Heart Association: Start!, 2009 (Box 45)
  - Joint Message, 2009; 58
    - East West Bank/First 5 LA: Ready Set Grow! Family Guide, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Ford/Komen for the Cure: Warriors in Pink, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Ford/Komen for the Cure: Warriors in Pink, 2009 (Box OV1)
    - Honeywell/National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: Got 2B Safe!, 2009 (Box 46)
    - HGTV/Multiple nonprofits: Change the World Start at Home, 2009 (Box 46)
    - L'Oréal/Ovarian Cancer Research Fund: Color of Hope, 2009 (Box 46)
  - Message-focused Campaign, 2009; 59
    - Ben & Jerry's/Freedom to Marry: Hubby Hubby Ice Cream, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Cargill (Honeysuckle White and Shady Brook Farms brands)/Feeding America: Cargill Holiday 2009 (Box 46)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center: Cycle for Survival, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Payless ShoeSource/Nature Conservancy: Payless Helps the Nature Conservancy Plant a Billion Trees (Zoe Zac launch), 2009 (Box 46)
    - RADD (Recording Artists, Actors and Athletes Against Drunk Driving): Hit the Road TXT L8TR, 2009; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Scholastic Book Club/Multiple nonprofits: Classrooms Care, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Scholastic Book Club/Multiple nonprofits: Classrooms Care, 2009 (Box OV7)
  - Multiple Categories, 2009; 60
    - AT&T/Rock the Vote, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Barefoot Wine/Surfrider Project: Barefoot Wine Beach Rescue Project, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Cheesecake Factory/Feeding America: Drive Out Hunger, 2009 (Box 47)
    - FedEx/Christmas Spirit Foundation: Trees for Troops, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Ferrero Rocher/Share Our Strength: Share Something Sweet, 2009 (Box 47)
    - General Mills/CARE: Join My Village--Women are Changing the World Village By Village--Join Us, 2009 (Box 47)
    - General Mills (Cheerios)/WomenHeart: Cheerios Circle of Helping Hearts, 2009; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - LeadDog Marketing/New York City Department of Transportation: Summer Streets, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Northwest Energy Efficiency Alliance: Be an Energy Star, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Northwest Energy Efficiency Alliance: Be an Energy Star, 2009 (Box OV1)
    - Scholastic Media/Hands On Institute: Clifford Be Big Campaign, 2009; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Scholastic Media/Hands On Institute: Clifford Be Big Campaign, 2009 (Box OV5)
    - Scholastic Media/Hands On Institute: Clifford Be Big Campaign, 2009; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Scholastic Media/Points of Light Institute: Clifford the Dog "Be Big" Campaign, 2009 (Box 48)
    - Sephora/Girls for a Change: Sephora Project, 2009; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Street Attack/Ashoka Youth Venture: Best Buy @15 Challenge, 2009; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Street Attack/Ashoka Youth Venture: Best Buy @15 Challenge, 2009 (Box OV5)
  - National/Local Integration, 2009; 61
    - Aramark/United Neighborhood Centers of America: Building Community, 2009 (Box 48)
    - Burlington Coat Factory/Leukemia and Lymphoma Society: Light the Night Walk, 2009 (Box 48)
    - Cone/Jiffy Lube/American Heart Association: Maintenance Partners for Life, 2009; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Ford/Komen for the Cure: Warriors in Pink, 2009 (Box 49)
    - General Mills (Betty Crocker)/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Stirring Up Wishes, 2009 (Box 49)
    - Hyundai/Leukemia and Lymphoma Society: Hyundai Hope on Wheels, 2009 (Box 49)
    - IHOP/Children's Miracle Network, 2009 (Box 49)
    - Jumpstart: Read for the Record, 2009; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - KPMG: Reviving Baseball in Inner Cities, 2009 (Box 49)
    - Lee Jeans/National Breast Cancer Coalition/Right Action for Women: Lee National Denim Day, 2009 (Box 49)
    - MLS/NBA/United Nations Foundation: Nothing but Nets (malaria), 2009 (Box 49)
    - PowerPact/Komen for the Cure: I Am the Cure, 2009 (Box 49)
    - Sears/Heroes at Home: Heroes At Home Gift Registry, 2009; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2009; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Toys R Us/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Make a Difference, 2009 (Box 50)
    - Toys R Us/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Make a Difference, 2009 (Box OV5)
    - UPS Store/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Toys for Tots Literacy Program, 2009; 4 folders (Box 50)
    - Western Union/Mercy Corps: Our World, Our Family, 2009 (Box 50)
  - Print Creative, 2009; 62
    - Del Monte/Safeway: Power of Paws, 2009 (Box 51)
    - H&R Block/DECA: Dollars and Sense, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Lee Jeans/Entertainment Industry Foundation: Lee National Denim Day, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Macy's/Make-a-Wish Foundation: A Million Reasons to Believe, 2009; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - New England Confectionary Co. (NECCO)/United Service Organization (USO): Sweethearts Red White and You, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Sears/Heroes at Home, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2009; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Toys R Us/National Lekotek Center: Toy Guide for Differently Abled Kids, 2009 (Box 51)
    - TracyLocke/The Family Place, 2009 (Box 51)
  - Social Media, 2009; 63
    - AOL (America OnLine)/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Nice One!, 2009 (Box 52)
    - Sears/Heroes at Home, 2009 (Box 52)
    - TripAdvisor: More than Footprints, 2009; 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2009; 64
    - Aeropostale/Do Something: Teens for Jeans, 2009 (Box 52)
    - Hear the World, 2009 (Box 52)
    - Honeywell/U.S. Space and Rocket Center: Honeywell Educators at Space Academy, 2009 (Box 52)
    - L'Oréal/Ovarian Cancer Research Foundation: Women of Worth, 2009; 3 folders (Box 52)
    - NFL Network/National Association on Sport and Physical Education (NASPE): Keep Gym in School, 2009 (Box 52)
    - PowerPact/Komen for the Cure: I Am the Cure, 2009 (Box 52)
    - PowerPact/Komen for the Cure: I Am the Cure, 2009 (Box 53)
    - Procter & Gamble (Always, Tampax)/Protecting Futures: UNA-USA Hero Partnership, 2009 (Box 53)
    - Red Sky/J.A. and Kathryn Albertson Foundation: Go On Campaign, 2009 (Box 53)
    - Samsung: Samsung's Hope for Education, 2009 (Box 53)
    - Sears/Heroes at Home, 2009 (Box 53)
    - Toys R Us/National Lekotek Center: Toy Guide for Differently Abled Kids, 2009 (Box 53)
    - UPS Store/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Toys for Tots Literacy Program, 2009; 4 folders (Box 53)